clapsnslaps.com 2017-02-11

# Movie Blog | Hindi Movie Blog | Cinema Blog | Bollywood Blog | Entertainment Blog | Picture Blog | CNS

The following statements explain the website’s policy regarding the personal information we collect about you when you use the website. This Privacy Policy explains our information collection practices at clapsnslaps.com, and our other interactive properties, including but not limited to our mobile websites and applications and through offline means. 

Thus this Privacy Policy applies to information we collect via (1) the Application (however accessed and/or used, whether via personal computers, mobile devices or otherwise); (2) email or electronic newsletters; (3) offline means such as telephone and traditional mail; and (4) any other means or applications in which you connect with us. 

The website is committed to ensuring the privacy of customers', consumers' and online visitors' personal information as your privacy is important for us. This policy may be reviewed at any time and it is recommended you review our policy any time you intend to supply your personal information to us. By using this website you agree to this policy, accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy and our terms and conditions from time to time issued. 

We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us. 

The website collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name, gender and telephone number and alike. 

We may use your personal information as u participate in our contests (VIP Nights) or any other and forums, sign ups, join our newsletters, email lists, other notifications on social networking websites login or request some other service or information from us. 

When your information is provided with feedback on our website, we will use the personal information to ascertain if this feedback is common to other listeners of similar gender and age groups, and see how successfully we are providing services to our target audience. 

If you access our Services on your mobile telephone or other mobile device, we also collect your unique device identifier and may collect location information. We also may collect your telephone number and other information you choose to provide, such as username or e-mail address (e.g., to receive updates about movies and other content). 

Under no circumstances will the website pass your personal information onto outside organisations except for the purpose in which they are intended to or there is a duty to the public to disclose that information, we are required to by law, or where the interests of the website require disclosure. 

You may opt out of receiving one or all of our communication services at any time by clicking on the link [unsubscribe](https://www.clapsnslaps.com/privacy#). 

If you click on a link to another website from clapsnslaps.com, you will need to refer to that other website’s privacy conditions as our privacy policy will no longer apply. 

This site makes space for opinion polls, individual reviews/ chat rooms and/or news available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

Please note that the information that you wish to make it public is not covered in the Privacy Policy, we do not control who will have access to the information that you choose to make public, and cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information that you disclose publicly, share with others or otherwise upload. We are not responsible for the accuracy, use or misuse of any content or information that you disclose or receive through such disclosure. 

We have incorporated safeguards to help prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. However, no data transmission over the Internet, wireless transmission or electronic storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and we cannot anticipate all potential misuse of data over the Internet. Please note that we cannot ensure the security of any information you transmit to us, and your use of website indicates that you are willing to assume this risk. 

If you choose to access the website, subscribe to our newsletters or use any of our Services, any dispute over privacy is subject to our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the laws of the Republic of INDIA. This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties. 

This website is a general audience website and is not intended to use by children. On the website, we do not currently knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of seventeen (17) If, in the future, we collect personally identifiable information from children on the Website, we will do so in compliance with all relevant laws and regulations and we will delete any Personal Information collected that we later determine to be from a user younger than the age of seventeen (17). If you believe a child under the age of seventeen (17) has disclosed Personal Information to us [info@clapsnslaps.com](mailto:rumit.anand@clapsnslaps.com)

Cookies" are small pieces of information that a website sends to the computer's hard drive while you are viewing a website. These are employed to gather the data. 

Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, and to save your login information so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our website. Information collected using cookies is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies using your web browser, but please be aware that for some parts of our websites to work, you will need to accept cookies. Cookies can be removed or declined by changing your web browser settings. 

We work with various third party advertising networks. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by advertising network, and we do not have access to this information.
